# DAMMU KIRAN

# **MERN FullStack Developer**

939 020 5169

dammukiran4@gmail.com

- Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh
- https://dammu-portfolio.vercel.app/
- www.linkedin.com/in/dammu-kiran-2605d
- https://github.com/kirandammu?tab=repositories

# **ABOUT ME**

I am very passionate to learn mernstack all Technologies. I build a user friendly responsive websites with good efficiency. I build more than of 10+ projects . I am interested to face the challenges and problem solving skills. I have I year experience in Mernstack technologies as a freelancer

#### **EDUCATION**

# DEGREE (BSC)

73%

SVLNS Govt Degree College 2020 - 2023

(MPC) INTER

90%

Sri Basara Junior College 2018-2020

SSC (10TH)

90%

Z P High School 2017-2018

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

# FRONTEND

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- TailwindCSS

#### BACKEND

- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- MongoDB
- JWT
- API PostMon Socket.io

# OTHER

- Git & GitHub
- Responsive WebDesign
- VS\_Code Editor
- NPM Packages

# **STRENGHTS**

- I'm a Quick Learner
- Self-Motivated Person
- Time Punctuality

# **LANGUAGE**

Telugu

English

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### WNS GLOBAL SERVICES

2024-NOW

**Operations Associate Role** 

I am worked as a associate role and strongly understanding of business operations, and maintain the time management and team work. I build a user friendly responsive websites with good efficiency.

#### FREELANCING

2024-NOW

build more than 10+ projects in Mernstack from scratch to advance. I am very passionate to learn everything and projects are deployed in online

#### **PROJECTS**

# **ECOMMERCE WEBSITE USING MERNSTACK WITH REDUX**

Online Ecommerce Website using mernstack with redux in this project all features are added like user authentication and images stored in cloudinary platform with Admin Panel for adding Products.

# SOCIAL MEDIA APPLICATION WITH CHATTING FEATURE

Social Media Application With Chatting Feature using mernstack with Socket.io . This project is available on all features like a user can upload post, comments, follow and chat to Everyone one

# ONLINE FOOD RESTAURANT ORDERS LIKE SWIGGY CLONE

Online Food Restaurant Orders like Swiggy Clone Application build With MERN stack all features available like place order and online stripe payment and cart is also available. This project is available on Admin Panel also Every Hotel Management add their food collection in our online store.

#### ONLINE CHAT APPLICATION USING SOCKET.IO

Online Chat Application is user friendly and fastly communication to anyone. we can build using mernstack with socket.io . Group Chat is also available on this application. and delete account and block to anyone all features all available.